#### Contact

+886917197882 (Mobile) dablog@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/juchunko (LinkedIn)

# Top Skills

Interaction Design Entrepreneurship

Mobile Applications

## Languages

Chinese (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional) Japanese (Limited Working)

#### Honors-Awards

IdeaMaker Prize - TechCrunch Disrupt 2014

Intel Prize - Startup Weekend Bay Area Makers 2014

Taipei City Government Award @ Yahoo Open Hack Day Taiwan 2013

Mobile Category Award @ Facebook World Hack Day 2012 Taipei (Worldwide)

Category Award @ The 1st Nintendo 3DS 3D Photo Contest (JAPAN)

#### **Publications**

Public issues on projected user interface.

Authorship and Liquidity in Wikiart.

Interactive Guiding Interface for 360-degree Virtual Reality Video Browsing: A case study of Cardboard VR.

Enabling Beyond Surface Interactions for Interactive Surface with An Invisible Projection.

Interactive Guiding Interface for 360-degree Virtual Reality Video Browsing: A case study of Cardboard VR

# JU CHUN (JC) KO

Innovation Technologist . Exponential Strategist Taipei City, Taipei City, Taiwan

# Summary

Ph.D. in Computer Science.

Computer Vision Lab in National Taiwan University; Singularity University (NASA Campus) research on CV, AI & Blockchain;

Postdoc Researcher in Keio University (JP) on VR and Telepresence;

Consulting Member of CoolBitX, Ubitus Inc. and Blueprint Japan; EmTech Consulting Member of Ministry of Economic Affairs, Taipei City Government and National Palace Museum.

# Experience & Award

- Blockchain topic film 《The Last Thieves》in Asia (TW, CN, JP)
- LUNA 360 Camera on Indiegogo and crowdfunded USD\$350K
- HTC Investment for Memora Inc. as HTC VIVEX Batch2
- Book《Moonshot Thinking(放膽射月)》
- TAVAR: Taiwan Assoc. of Virtual and Augmented Reality
- TAICHI: ACM SIGCHI Taipei Chapter
- SingularityU Taiwan Ambassador
- Keynote speaker in Taipei Arena w/ over 10K audiences
- Yahoo Open Hack Day Taiwan 2013 Taipei City Gov Award
- FB World Hack Day 2012 Taipei Mobile Category Award
- Linkwish, Inc. in 2011, over 2M downloads in Taiwan App Store.
- Digital Art Festival Taipei/ KT Award Winner for 4 years. (2007 2011)
- IndieCade: Independent Arcade Festival (U.S.A) Finalists. (2008)

# Experience

## 國立臺灣大學

Adjunct Assistant Professor August 2021 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Graduate Institute of Networking and Multimedia

#### **Patents**

Panoramic Image Capturing Device Wearable Interactive Card 360-Degree Image Pickup Apparatus Housed In A Spherical Housing

Panorama Image Capture Apparatus

360 Degree Image Capture Apparatus Enclosed in A Ball-shape Housing NM5631 Virtual Human and Telepresence

NM5371 Decentralized Applications Design and Practice

## dentsu 電通行銷傳播集團

Web3 Growth Partner

August 2022 - Present (1 year 7 months)

Bringing blockchain technology, Web3 trends, NFT and metaverse strategies to enterprises and brands.

#### 國立臺北科技大學

**Assistant Professor** 

June 2018 - July 2022 (4 years 2 months)

Taipei City, Taiwan

Department of Interaction Design

Teaching Blockchain, Virtual Reality and Metaverse

Memora Inc.

Co-Founder

July 2014 - August 2014 (2 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

Merging 360 imaging technology with Deep Learning AI technology.

Creating LUNA, the new camera like GoPro for VR.

Singularity University

**GSP Program** 

July 2014 - August 2014 (2 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

Exponential Technology and Exponential Thinking in NASA Ames Research

Park.

Space Technology, Wearable Technology, DeepLearning AI, VR & Robotics.

Leo Burnett

Sr. Planner of Social & Digital

August 2013 - July 2014 (1 year)

Taiwan

Responsible for international top-tier customers such as Samsung.

Linkwish Inc.

CEO & Co-Founder

January 2011 - December 2012 (2 years)

Taiwan

A leading Mobile App company in Taiwan.

Changed name to MobileWish afterward.

Shih Chien University, Institute of Communications Design Adjunct Assistant Professor September 2011 - August 2012 (1 year)

Taipei

Ranked as Top30 design schools in the world by Businessweek and Ranker.com.

National Taiwan University
Adjunct Instructor
2005 - 2008 (3 years)
Computer & Information Networking Center

# Education

#### Keio University

Postdoc Researcher, Media Design · (January 2014 - August 2014)

## **Babson College**

SEE Asia 2015 - Symposium for Entrepreneurship

Educators, Entrepreneurship/Entrepreneurial Studies · (2015 - 2015)

#### National Taiwan University

Ph. D in Computer Science, Networking and Multimedia, Image and Vision Lab · (2005 - 2011)

#### Yuan-Ze University

Master of Informatics, College of Informatics, Dept. of Information and Communication · (2003 - 2005)

#### Tamkang University

Bachelor of Art, Dept. of Information and Communication  $\cdot$  (1999 - 2003)